http://www.newline.com.au/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
HomePrivacy Policy & Terms
About UsOur ServicesDrupal Website DevelopmentGoogle ServicesWeb HostingBusiness SupportWork GalleryFAQsContact
24/7 Support
We are here when you need us.
Free Minor Mods
We don't charge for them.
Experience
20 years in web development.
No Jargon
We speak your language.
Collection and Disclosure of Personal Information
Newline Digital (formerly Newline Development) has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. Any information collected by Newline Digital from emails or web site forms will not be sold, rented, traded or otherwise supplied to any third party without your consent.
Sensitive information
Newline Digital does not collect sensitive information such as your race, religion, beliefs, health status or sexual preference except where you have consented or where we are permitted or required by law to do so.
Website cookies
The Newline Digital web site makes limited use of "cookies" technology. We use cookies to improve the functionality of our web site, not to store any of your personal information. Cookies cannot determine the identity of individual users. It is a feature of your Internet browser which you can disable at any time, but if you disable this feature you may not be able to access all of the functionality of our web site.
Security
Newline Digital takes all reasonable steps to protect the security of the personal information that we hold. This includes appropriate measures to protect electronic materials and materials stored and generated in hard copy.
Newline Digital Is Ready For Your Next Project
Web design, Google services, Internet services and more ...
Contact Us Today
